{
    "subject": "resource/Zainab_Biisheva",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Orenburg_Governorate",
    "human_readable": "Zainab Biisheva was born in Orenburg Governorate.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9825452566146851,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in Orenburg Governorate during Zainab Biisheva's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9350441098213196,
            "question": "Where was Zainab Biisheva born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.861108660697937,
            "question": "What year was Zainab Biisheva born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7547551393508911,
            "question": "What is the significance of being born in Orenburg Governorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7455735802650452,
            "question": "Are there any famous people who were also born in Orenburg Governorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7088764309883118,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Zainab Biisheva's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6169159412384033,
            "question": "Is there any historical information about Zainab Biisheva?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5682332515716553,
            "question": "What is Orenburg Governorate known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5351439714431763,
            "question": "Does Zainab Biisheva have any known relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46716171503067017,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Orenburg Governorate?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zainab Biisheva was born in Orenburg Governorate.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3054_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Zainab Biisheva have any known relatives?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3054_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Orenburg Governorate known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3054_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any historical information about Zainab Biisheva?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3054_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3054_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Zainab Biisheva was born in the village of Tuembetovo, which is now part of the Kugarchinsky district of Bashkortostan. There is no mention of Orenburg Governorate.  "
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does not mention that Zainab Biisheva was born in Orenburg Governorate. In fact, her birthplace is mentioned as the village of Tuembetovo (now - Kugarchinsky district of Bashkortostan) in one of the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information indicating that Zainab Biisheva was born in Orenburg Governorate. Her birthplace is given as the village of Tuembetovo, which is now part of the Kugarchinsky district of Bashkortostan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Zainab Biisheva was born in the Kugarchinsky district of Bashkortostan, not in Orenburg Governorate.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Zainab Biisheva was born in the village of Tuembetovo (now Kugarchinsky district of Bashkortostan).",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information about Zainab Biisheva mentions her village of birth (Tuembetovo, now Kugarchinsky district of Bashkortostan), but it does not mention Orenburg Governorate as her place of birth.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Zainab Biisheva was born in the village of Tuembetovo, which is now part of the Kugarchinsky district of Bashkortostan, not Orenburg Governorate.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}